[
	{ "question": "Are you safe ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Yes", "qLink": 1 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":911 }] },
	{ "question": "Where were you ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "-1", "qLink": 2 }] },
	{ "question": "Were you inside or Outside ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "inside", "qLink": 3 }, { "ans": "Outside", "qLink":3 }] },
	{ "question": "When was this ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Night-time", "qLink": 4 }, { "ans": "Day-time", "qLink":4 }] },
	{ "question": "Did it happen today ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Yes", "qLink": 5 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":7 }] },
	{ "question": "Would you like help ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Yes", "qLink": 911 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":7 }] },
	{ "question": "Do you remember the day ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "-1", "qLink": 8 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":8 }] },
	{ "question": "Do you remember the month ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "-1", "qLink": 9 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":9 }] },
	{ "question": "Do you remember the year ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "-1", "qLink": 10 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":10 }] },
	{ "question": "Do you know this person ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Yes", "qLink": 11 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":16 }] },
	{ "question": "Do you know their name ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Yes", "qLink": 12 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":12 }] },
	{ "question": "Are they family or friend ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Family", "qLink": 13 }, { "ans": "Friend", "qLink":13 }] },
	{ "question": "Is this the first time this has happened ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Yes", "qLink": 14 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":0 }] },
	{ "question": "How many times has this occured ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "-1", "qLink": 15 }, { "ans": "First Time", "qLink":0 }] },
	{ "question": "Were they male or female ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Male", "qLink": 16 }, { "ans": "Female", "qLink":16 }] },
	{ "question": "What was their height ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Shorter than me", "qLink": 17 }, { "ans": "About the same height as me", "qLink":17 }, { "ans": "Taller than me", "qLink":17 }] },
	{ "question": "What was their race ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "African American", "qLink": 18 }, { "ans": "American Indian/Alaskan Native", "qLink":18 }, { "ans": "Caucasian", "qLink":18 }, { "ans": "Asian", "qLink":18 }, { "ans": "Native Hawaiian/Other Pacific Islander", "qLink":18 }] },
	{ "question": "What was the color of their clothing ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "-1", "qLink": 19 }] },
	{ "question": "Are you willing to go into detail ?", "answer": [{ "ans": "Yes", "qLink": 20 }, { "ans": "No", "qLink":0 }] }
]